Have you solved all the problems?
Yes.
Where are we going next?
Where do you want to go?
I'll go with you.
How about
Dali Erhai?
Okay.
I know you are Su Muli.
I also know how Su Muchen died.
Now you want revenge.
I'm the only one who can help you.
Who are you?
How can you help me?
I can be your shadow.
I can be your eyes and hands in the Lu family
without being noticed by anyone.
I need to let Zhou Jian know about the Chinese female fencer.
I need a chance to meet her.
I'm here for a business trip.
I heard that
there is a
a very good female fencer here.
I was defeated by you today.
Fencing is an art,
not a competition.
But it's also a happy thing
to meet you.
What's your name?
What a beautiful bracelet!
Why is Zhou Jian?
Zhou Jian has his purpose.
His marriage with Lu Qianqian
[is like a cracked glass from the start.]
[It will break into pieces]
[with a little force.]
Lu Qianqian is looking for you.
Tell her I'm in the bathroom.
[I've placed the bug in the frame]
[as you instructed.]
Now, I just await Zhou Jian and the Lu family.
[to fall into the trap I've set up.]
So,
[those so-called designers]
[don't know me as well as you do.]
[I've decided]
[to let Jiang Li]
[design my wedding dress.]
[I believe]
[Jiang Li will make me]
[the most dazzling bride.]
Go to school first.
I'll play with you
after you get back.
[Lu Qianqian has found out about the perfume.]
[Your plan can move to the next stage.]
[In your script,]
[Lu Xu and Li Xiaorou]
[should make their appearance.]
[The plot of Dark Fairy Tale]
[is about to reach its climax.]
Yan.
Yes?
Take out the autumn clothes from my cloakroom
and iron them.
and put two pairs of shoes
in the suitcase.
Yes, madam.
Li,
this is a present for you.
You're back from Singapore so soon.
What a beautiful dress.
Lefkisitine,
you like this perfume too?
Jiang Li, are you ready?
Zhou Jian will be back soon.
He knows our secret.
At this time,
shouldn't you
take Mumu to school?
You help me with all your might.
Aren't you afraid of jumping into the abyss with me?
I've already been in the abyss and can't get out.
Su Muchen was also involved in my selfishness.
Helping you
is my redemption.
If I hadn't provided Su Muchen with the information,
maybe
she wouldn't have died.
On the night of my sister's accident,
did Zhou Jian really hesitate
to save her?
After Su Muchen had the accident,
Zhou Jian rushed to the scene immediately.
She was still alive at that time.
But when Zhou Jian picked up the phone
and was about to call the police,
he hesitated.
Someone had a car accident.
Save him.
How did you know?
Because
I was the second one to arrive at the scene.
Liu Yanyan,
I always feel you are not as simple as you appear.
Who is
your enemy?
My enemy is the same as yours.
[the Lu family,]
[the Yao family,]
[and]
[the Shen family]
[from Wensheng Group.]
You've been hovering around me for ages,
just making tea for me.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
You've always set the rule
that the Shen Family
shouldn't get involved in Golden Thread.
Now I think
you must have known
Annie would end up like this.
But
you're too indulgent
to Jingmo.
Rules are dead,
but people are alive.
Whether to break them
or how to break them
is up to you young folks.
I'm
almost half in the ground,
just a few strands of hair left breathing.
If I were to meddle in everything,
I'd be powerless to do so.
You,
are being overly modest.
Everyone knows
you're the most powerful hunter
in this city.
Even the wolves in the forest
would go out of their way to avoid you.
Xiaowan,
after Shen Zhong's death,
technically,
you and Xiao Chu
shouldn't have stayed in the core circle.
Do you know why I kept you by my side?
How could I
understand your intentions?
When I was 16,
my father gave me
a silver ring
as my capital.
Step by step,
I got where I am today.
What did I rely on?
Not luck,
but ambition.
and a huge ambition.
I kept you by my side
because I see your ambition.
In Shen Family,
only the fittest survive.
If you're capable,
hold everything of Shen Family
in your own hands,
then
it will be yours.
If you don't have the ability,
just be content
to be a stepping stone
for the true heir of the Shen Family.
So,
is this a test
or your true thoughts?
Are you serious?
I won't help Jingmo,
nor will I help you.
Whoever is more capable
whoever wins in the end
will be qualified
to take over the Shen Family.
Jingmo
dares to trade Ruisheng Technology,
which he founded, for the Golden Thread
to win a smile from a beauty.
That's his determination and courage.
What about you?
Zhuang Wan,
in the face of his determination,
to face his determination?
If you dare,
you have the right to be on the table
to compete with me.
OK.
With your words,
I can break the rules
with confidence.
Go ahead.
Anyway,
when I close my eyes
and kick the bucket,
all I'll have left is a small piece of land.
Whether you squander the Shen Family's fortune
or take it to greater heights,
it'll have
nothing to do
with me.
Ah.
Then you just keep fishing.
I'll go
handle something.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Well,
ask Mr. Xiao
to bring me some new bait.
The fish here
are picky.
Okay.
Got it.
Hello?
Have you decided?
I can help you
get Shen Jingmo back
from Jiang Li.
In exchange,
I need you to use
all the resources of Hongshou Insurance
to help me
regain control
of Golden Thread at all costs.
Alright.
I promise you.
As long as you give me what I want,
you can get what you want.
Okay.